Guide to the Stanford University, El Centro Chicano, Records SC0650
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional materials, Accession ARCH-2005-210
  - Foundations
    - Nest Foundation, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - The David & Lucille Packard Foundation (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Central America
    - Interplast, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Nicaragua Hospital generator Project, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - OXFAM, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - PASMAC, 1985-87 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - WestCAN, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - VFW Bill Motto Post 5888/VSA, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Sanctuary (Nationwide), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Teatro de la Esperanza, 1983-84 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Teatro de la Esperanza Proposals, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Program Proposals Winter, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Hispanic Organizations
    - AIDS, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Aztlan Cultural, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Bay Area Colleges: Ethnic Studies, Employment Opps., 1989-90 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Bay Area Higher Education Network, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Bay Area Directory of Job Placement Services for Minorities, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - California RAZA/Latino Medical Student Association, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Centro Bilingue (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Central American Crisis Resources, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Centro de Intercambio Cultural de Cuernavaca, A.C., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Chicano Professional Organizations, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Hispanic Democrats of Sacramento (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Hispanic Initiative/Red Cross, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Hispanic Leaders in Los Angeles (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Hispanic Organizations, 39973 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Immigration Assistance, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Instituto de Estudios, 1984-85 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Inter-University Program for Latino Research, 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Latino Agenda Coalition "Organizing for Latino Ed. Rights", 1986 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Mexican-American Community Services Agency, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - The California Museum of Latino History, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Mission Cultural Center, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - National Association for Chicano Studies, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - National Council of La Raza, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - RAZA Advocates for California Higher Education (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Spanish Speaking Unity Council, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Union y Progreso, Inc., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - UCLA - Applied Humanities in Chicano Studies Program (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Ventana Spanish Language Program, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Vista Magazine (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Non-Stanford Offices & Organizations
    - American Red Cross- Hispanic Health Ed. Project, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - American Red Cross, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Anheuser Busch Companies, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Apple Business Forum, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - California Coalition on University/Community Services, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - California Independent Colleges & Universities, 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - California Literacy Campaign, 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Campus Outreach Opportunity league, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Center for Third World Organizing, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Communications Academy, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - ACU-I COMP West Coast Committees, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - Coors company, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - DQ University, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Directory of Select California Fellowship/Internship Program, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - ETS/Education and Career Needs of Latinos, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Family Service Association, 1986-86 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Foothill DeAnza District, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - General Info: 5-year graduation Rates, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Good Samaritan Community Cutural Center, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Harvard MBA, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Hughes Aircraft Co., 1986 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - HHS Public Affairs Directory, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Indians, Promises, and us, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Jesse Unruh Assembly program, 1988-89 (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - la Raza graphics center, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - mid Peninsula Peace center, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - National Hispanic Heritage Week, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Neighborhood Arts Fund, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - PROCOMEXCHI Governor Cardenas, 1985-86 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Proctor & Gamble, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Racial & Ethnic Relations in American Higher Education, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Raza Admininstrations & Counselors in Higher Education, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - Senate office of Research, 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - Special Committee on Educational Equity, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - Special events, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - youth development center, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - Stanford Bookstore, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - Operating Budget Fund Transfers, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - Printing/Copying Service, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - Hard Drive, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 106)
    - Salaried Employee Adjustment, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - Key Policy/Keys, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 108)
    - El Centro Deposited Needed, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Interdepartmental Requests, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 110)
    - Transfer of Expense, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - Chicano Student Organizations, 1987-1988
    - Core Committee, 1987-88 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Barrio Assistance, 1987-88 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Buddy Program, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Chicano Graduation, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Chicano Graduate Students Association, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Chicano Orientation, 1987-88 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Chicano Student Activities Committee, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Estos Tiempos, 1987-88 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Latino Student Organizations, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Project Motivation (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - SAlsA, 1989-90 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Chicano Student Organizations, 1986-1987
    - Chicano Graduation, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Chicano Grad Student Assn (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Chicano Fellows, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Chicano Faculty, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - CORE Committee, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - CORE Committee, 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Casa Zapata, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Barrio Assistance, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Alpha Chi Alpha, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Chicano Student Organizations, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - CSAC, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - CHIPS and SALsA, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - CSAC External Fundraising Proposal, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - CSAC, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - CSAC Annual Fundraising proposal, 1987-88 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - El Conjunto, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Latino Business Society, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Estos Tiempos, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Project Motivation, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - CORE Committee, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - La Raza Law, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - MEChA Conference, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - SALI, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - SaLSA, 1987-88 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - SSCLES, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Workers' Cultural Celebration, 1986-97 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Chicano Student Organizations, 1984-1985
    - CHE, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - CHALE (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Chicano Studies Organization, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - SSCES, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Comite Pro Lenguaje Chicano, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Teatro Sin Verguenza (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - VSO Chicano Latino, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Anti Bakke Decision Coalition (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Assocation of Mexican Students at Stanford (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Chicano Law Student Association, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Chicano Graduate Student Association, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Chicano Student Organizations, 1969, 1980, 1990
    - Chicano Med Students' Association, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Chicano Pre Law (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Patricia Roberts Harris Conference, 33211 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Puerto Rican Students Association, 1986-90 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Puerto Rican Assocation (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Puerto Rican Student Assoctiation (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Puerto Rican Association, 1979-80 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Instituto Allende, 1980-81 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Chicano Student Organizations, 1985-1986
    - Chicano Organizations- Descriptions, 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Alpha Chi Alpha, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Chicano Faculty, 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Graduating Chicano Seniors, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Chicano Fellows, 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Chicano Orientation, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Chicano Student Activities Committee, 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Comite Latino, 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - CORE Committee, 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Chicano Graduation, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Chicano Graduation (2), 1986 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - SALI, 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Project Motivation, 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Career Week, 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Chicano Student Organizations, 1984-1985
    - Association of Mexican Students @ Stanford, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Ballet Folklorico, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Barrio Assistance, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - La Chicana Colectiva (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - La Chicana Colectiva, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Chicano Graduate Student Association, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Chicano Graduation Committee, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - Chicano Pre-Laws, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 78)
    - MEChA, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 79)
    - Chicano Pre Meds, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 80)
    - Chicano Student Activities Committee, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 81)
    - CSAC finance (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - Latino Business Society, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - Stanford Raza Medical Association, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 84)
    - SSCES, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - Spring Programs (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Performing Arts
    - ALMA Tropical, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 87)
    - California Arts Council Touring Directory, 1988-89 (Box 13, Folder 88)
    - California Arts Council Touring Directory, 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    - Chicano Film, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    - Pro MO, 1986-87 (Box 13, Folder 91)
    - Encuentro Del Canto Popular, 1984-90 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - "The Denial", Gregory Sagar, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - Films, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - Galeria De la Raza, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - institute for Salsa & Jazz Development, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Linda Haim & her Puppets, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - Maldonado Management, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - Mariachis, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - The Marimba Tradition of Latin America, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Budget, 1989
    - 1987-88 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Budget, 1988
    - Budget Statement Category Definitions (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Budget, 1988-89 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Budget Request, 1988-89 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Estos Tiempos ASSU Loan, 1988-89 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - General Planning & Improvement Request, 1988-89 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Renovation Project, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1987-1988
    - Budget Folder, 1987-88 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Budget Savings Account, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Centro Budget Request: 5 Year Budget Setting Processes, 1987-88 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - ASSU Loan To MEChA, 1987-88 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - El Centro Reserve Account, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Quarterly Expenditure Reports, 1987-88 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Budget, 1986-1987
    - One-Time Budget Request, 1986-87 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Full Time Centro Budget Requests (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Centro Long-Term Planning Document, 1986-87 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Copy Charges/Invoices, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Reciepts, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Reserve Account, 1986-87 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Closing Accounts, 1986-87 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Budget, 1985-1986
    - Receipts, 1985-86 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Budget Requests (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - ASSU Forms (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Budget, 1984-1985
    - FY-End Closing Budget, 1984-85 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Centro Budget (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - One-time Budget Request, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Financial Notes, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Budget, 1983-1984
    - Finances, 1983-84 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Budget, 1980-1981
    - Statements, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Budget, 1979-1980
    - Operating Budget Receipts (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - University Stores (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Interdepartmental Requests (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Key Policy/Keys (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Work Orders (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Telephone Statements (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Transfer of Expense (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Xerox Billings (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Transactions, 1988-1989
    - Copy Charges/Invoice (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Interdepartmental Requests, 1987-88 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Transfer of Requests, 1987-88 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - University Stores, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Work Information Order, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Transactions, 1987-1988
    - Transfer of Expense (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - University Stores (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Interdepartmental Requests (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Work Information Order (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Xerox Copy Billings (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Purchase Requisitions, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Transactions, 1986-1987
    - Transfer of Expense (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Interdepartmental Requests (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - University Stores (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Work Information Requests (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Telephones (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Transactions, 1985-1986
    - Purchase Requisitions (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Transfer of Expense (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - University Stores, 1985-86 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Work Information Orders (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Transactions, 1990-1991
    - Xerox Charges Autumn (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Transactions, 1989-1990
    - Purchase Requisitions (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - August (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence
    - Outgoing, 1988-89 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Chron File 87-88: Outgoing, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Chron File 87-88: Incoming (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Chron File 86-87: Incoming, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Chron File 86-87: Outgoing (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Chron. 85-86: Incoming, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Chron. 85-86 Outgoing (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Campus Affairs
    - DOSA Retreat, 1988-89 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Campus Affairs, 1988-89 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Campus Affairs Retreat Fall, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Residence Directory, 1988-89 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Bridge Space Report (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - DOSA Committee on Programs for Minority Students (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Photos, 1990-91 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Newsletter Masters, 1981-82 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Newsletter, 1984-85 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Unsorted
    - UCLA Mexican Arts Symposium 1985 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - You Can Make A Difference 88-89 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - George I. Sanchez Seminar 1985 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Openness to Difference 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Public Policy Research Forum 1988 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Third World Counselors Association Conference 1988 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Education: Taking Action For Our Future/Conference, May 14, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Chicano Literary Criticism in A Social Context 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - First Annual Chicano Youth Leadership Conference, Santa Clara University, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Chicano School Failure & Success, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Conference on Management Assistance For Culturally Diverse Arts Orgs, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - El Centro Fundraising 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Centro Dorm Reps 1990 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - El Centro Chicano VIP Mailing List, 1987-88 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Alumni (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Jeremy Warren, Human Resources Services (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Welcome Reception 10-11-91, El Centro Chicano (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Women Needs Assessment Group, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Misc. Mailing List 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Campus Affairs- Ed Fund 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Student and Police Relations 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Budget 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Budget Cuts 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Meetings with Paul 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Staff Meetings 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Grad Students Program Funds 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Guiding Concilio Poster (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Stanford Chicano Staff and Administration 1991 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Americas and Latinas Journal (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - El Aguila (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Noticias (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Opportunities for Ugrad Chicanos (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - El Centro Brochure (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Facilities, Jeanette Smith- Laws (90-91) (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Federal Work Study Programs 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - OMD/Multiculturalism Report. 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Porras-Readings in Mission Statements (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - News Clippings 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Chicano Community Events, Flyers 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - El Centro Programming (90-91) Centennial Year (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Graduation Information, 90-91 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Barrio Assistance Irvine Evaluation (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - CORE Retreat @ Buck Estate, 10/11/92 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - CGSA 91-92 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - CORE Meetings 91-92 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Chicano/Latino Student Groups 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Chicano/Latino Community Meeting (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Orientation Calendar (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Puerto Rican Students 91-92 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Stanford Chicano Visiting Faculty 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Summer Educational Advancement Program (SEAP) 91-92 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - RA Training 9/13-9/15, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - SEAP 5/20/91, Summer Program (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Minority Student Outreach Program 1990-91, Irvin Project (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Music & Politics 4/92 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - New Student Orientation (Ann Porteus), 1992-93 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Newsweek 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - New Students 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - New Students 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Office for Multicultural Development 1990-91 Activities Report (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Office of Student Activities Calendar of Events Request 8/25/91 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Oregon Health (F. Cuadros) 6/92, Sciences University (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Outreach-Hligh Schools Admissions 11/90 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - President of Mexico, Carlos Salinas de Gortari, 9/91 (Centennial) (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Prospective Frosh 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Pro Fro Week 4/90 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Public Service Career Faire 2/12/91 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Publications Office 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - La Raza Staff Association 1990, Interim Advisory Committee (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Readers-Admissions Office 11/16/90 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Linda Rios-The University of New Mexico 5/92 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Kimberly Ross-New Student Orientation Coordinator (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Registrar of Voters 6/5/90 (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - RF/RA Training Community Issues Forum 9/11/91 (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Report on Multicultural Education Development 1/90-4/91 (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Repositioning 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - J. Rosse Senate Statement 5/2/91 (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - SAC 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - SCCR-Job Announcement 6/90 (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - SDC 551-Intro to MAC Excel 8/5/91 (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - "So Are You Politically Correct? Contradictions in The Canon" 7/91 (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - Span Dept. 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - Sourcebook Mailout 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 84)
    - Stanford in Government 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 85)
    - Stanford 1990 Health Needs Assessment (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - Stanford University Centennial Celebration (Box 16, Folder 87)
    - Summer Programs at SU 1990 (Box 16, Folder 88)
    - Student Leadership Training 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 89)
    - SNAP Purchasing News 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 90)
    - STEP-School of Education 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 91)
    - R. Trujillo 10/7/91 (Box 16, Folder 92)
    - CLOC 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 93)
    - SU in Washington 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 94)
    - Telecommunications 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 95)
    - Tutoring Committee, Haas Center 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 96)
    - Leslie Townsend Winter 1991, Freshman English (Box 16, Folder 97)
    - Robert Trujillo-Green Library, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 98)
    - Undergraduate Admissions, 11/5/90 (Box 16, Folder 99)
    - VPSR Interviews, 4:15-5:15 Bldg. 200, Room 203, 10/91 (Box 16, Folder 100)
    - Patrick Velasquez 7/91, UC San Diego- Setting up Centro (Box 16, Folder 101)
    - YOP Certificate, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 102)
    - YOP- Certificate of Appreciation - 6/91 (Box 16, Folder 103)
    - You Can Make A Difference Conference, 1/26/91 (Box 16, Folder 104)
    - You Can Make A Difference 2/1/92 (Box 16, Folder 105)
    - Noticias Letters, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 106)
    - Leadership Summit 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Rosana Vasquez 1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Noticias - Letters 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Controlled Substances 1990-1991 And Alcohol (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Multiculturalism at SU Panel Discussion 4/19/1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - CPPC Careers in Social Change 1/16/90 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Webb Ranch-1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - ACOME 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - A.Martinez-Questionnaire 1/90 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Holsinger, Inc. Proposals (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - BCSC Constitution 2/9/90 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - "What Boards Do" (Keith Archuleta) 2/16/90 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - K. Archuleta Handouts 2/16/90 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Timeline 2/16/90 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - MeCha Proposal 2/90 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Mission 2/16/90 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Possible Governance Questions 2/16/90 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Questionnaire 1989 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Staff Questionnaire 1989 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Student Questionnaire 1989 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Chicano Colloquia 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Chicano Alumni 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Chicano Fellows (1988-1989) (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Chicana Staff 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Chicano Recruitment 1986 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - First Annual Galarza Prize 1988 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Galarza Community Service Internship 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Hispanic Freshmen 88-89 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Hispanic Leadership Opportunity PGM. 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Hispanic Leadership Opportunity PGM. 1987 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Hispanic Leadership Opportunity PGM. 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 31)